<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <Language_en_US>

    <!-- Civilization -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ELMONIA_DESC">
      <Text>Elmonian Empire</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ELMONIA_SHORT_DESC">
      <Text>Elmonia</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ELMONIA_ADJ">
      <Text>Elmonian</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_ELMONIA_PEDIA">
      <Text>A kingdom where pleasure is philosophy and beauty is law. Elmonia has long stood as a beacon of refined culture and golden prosperity.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILIZATION_ELMONIA">
      <Text>Elmonian Empire</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILIZATION_ELMONIA_PEDIA">
      <Text>An opulent civilization built on art, pleasure and military pageantry. Elmonia uses culture and charm to sway the world.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILIZATION_ELMONIA_PEDIA_TAG">
      <Text>Elmonia is ruled by a sovereign court that turns every conquest into a celebration of elegance.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILIZATION_ELMONIA_SHORT_DESC">
      <Text>Elmonia</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILIZATION_ELMONIA_ADJECTIVE">
      <Text>Elmonian</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_DAWN_ELMONIA_TEXT">
      <Text>Great Queen Emma XIV, radiant sovereign of Elmonia, your people have flourished for generations upon fertile islands blessed by gentle seas, rich vineyards, and abundant harvests. Under your reign, the pursuit of beauty, refinement, and life's finest pleasures has elevated Elmonia into a kingdom renowned throughout the world.
From your celebrated wine estates flow vintages coveted by kings and merchants alike. Grand festivals fill the calendar, and the halls of your palaces echo with music, laughter, and tales of courtly splendor. To the people of Elmonia, prosperity is measured not only in wealth, but in the joy and elegance with which life is lived.
Yet the realm is not without guardians. The noble Lunar Knights patrol your lands beneath silver banners, defending the kingdom with unwavering devotion. They are often led by your most faithful servant and trusted adviser, Ilpolius the Humble, whose loyalty to crown and country has become the subject of countless songs and legends.
Across the meadows and moonlit hills of Elmonia roam the mysterious Moonsteeds, a rare breed of horse distinguished by their graceful stature and singular brow-crests. Though foreign travelers often mistake them for creatures of myth, they have long served as companions to Elmonia's heroes and champions.
Now, Queen Emma XIV, the destiny of Elmonia rests in your hands. Will your kingdom's culture, prosperity, and celebrated pleasures endure through the ages? Will your Lunar Knights safeguard the realm against all who would threaten its peace? Can the glory of Elmonia shine brighter than any rival civilization?
Great Queen Emma XIV, lead your people to greatness, and build a civilization that will stand the test of time.</Text>
    </Row>

    <!-- Leader -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_EMMA_XIV">
      <Text>Emma XIV</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_EMMA_XIV_PEDIA">
      <Text>Emma XIV rules Elmonia with an iron will cloaked in silken luxury. Under her reign, pleasure and power are one.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_EMMA_XIV_PEDIA_TAG">
      <Text>Pleasure and power are one.</Text>
    </Row>

    <!-- Trait -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_ELMONIA_HEDONISM">
      <Text>Hedonist Rule</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_ELMONIA_HEDONISM_DESC">
      <Text>Each Luxury resource provides +2 additional [ICON_CULTURE] culture. Golden Ages last 50% longer.</Text>
    </Row>

    <!-- Unique Unit -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ELMONIA_LUNAR_KNIGHT">
      <Text>Lunar Knight</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ELMONIA_LUNAR_KNIGHT_PEDIA">
      <Text>Elite cavalry of Elmonia, sworn to pleasure and moonlit battle. Stronger than a standard Knight and trained to fight in open terrain.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ELMONIA_LUNAR_KNIGHT_STRATEGY">
      <Text>Use on the front lines. Slightly stronger than a standard Knight, with a bonus in open terrain thanks to Drill I.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ELMONIA_LUNAR_KNIGHT_HELP">
      <Text>Unique Elmonian unit. Replaces Knight. +2 [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat strength. Starts with Drill I.</Text>
    </Row>

    <!-- Unique Building -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOOL_OF_FRIENDSHIP">
      <Text>School of Friendship</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOOL_OF_FRIENDSHIP_PEDIA">
      <Text>The gleaming School of Friendship is study-center, feast-hall, and a line of defense, the heart of Elmonian civic life.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOOL_OF_FRIENDSHIP_STRATEGY">
      <Text>Build in every city for steady culture, happiness and science output and for extra defense.</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOOL_OF_FRIENDSHIP_HELP">
      <Text>Unique Elmonian building. Replaces University. +3 [ICON_SCIENCE] Science, +3 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness, +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, extra defense.</Text>
    </Row>

    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_CAPITAL">
      <Text>Hedon</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_2">
      <Text>Lunaria</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_3">
      <Text>Manehattan</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_4">
      <Text>Las Pegasus</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_5">
      <Text>Fillydelphia</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_6">
      <Text>Cloudsdale</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_7">
      <Text>Rarityville</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_8">
      <Text>Big Applejack</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_ELMONIA_9">
      <Text>Vanhoover</Text>
    </Row>

    <!-- Traits -->
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_HEDONISTIC_CULTURE">
      <Text> 
      [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Ages last 50% longer, 
      keep 50% happiness [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] even if trading last resource away,
      [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from Luxury resources increased by 2,
      Wonderproduction +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION].</Text>
    </Row>
    <Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_HEDONISTIC_CULTURE_SHORT">
      <Text>Hedonistic Culture</Text>
    </Row>
  </Language_en_US>
</GameData>